# EDUARDO PFLUCKER SOUSA

213 Manuel Vicente Villarán Chama – Surco, Lima 33, Peru Email: eduardopflucker@msn.com Home +51-1- 271-6599

Cell +51-1-997-568-731

# **QUALIFICATIONS SUMMARY**

A highly creative, 38 years of experienced goal-oriented professional with solid procurement & logistics knowledge. Demonstrated experience in project management, production procurement, logistics and transport, project and operation budgeting. Organized with the ability to manage multiple projects and meet deadlines. A strong work ethic combined with a commitment to excellence in all projects undertaken. A team player, working effectively with operations, financing, and senior management in accomplishing objectives.

### AREAS OF STRENGTH

PROCUREMENT MANAGEMENT – GLOBAL SOURCING - ON-LINE PROCUREMENT – CUSTOM CLEARANCE - LOGISTICS & TRANSPORT – WAREHOUSE INVENTORY MANAGEMENT

## PROCUREMENT & LOGISTICS EXPERTISE

- Significant experience in local and overseas procurement, e-procurement and Worldwide logistics for projects and operation with just-on-time delivery.
- Excellent relation with well known Suppliers for Gas and Oil Industry, Tubular manufactures and Power Generation Plants.
- Ability to understand Operations and Maintenance requirements analyze their necessities and assist them in planning strategies to achieve results within the established company procedures.
- Proven experience with special transportation requirements to remote areas, by air, ocean, river or land.
- Coordination of logistics and management of special projects.
- Experience in implementing Logistics-Materials-Maintenance Integrated Software.
- High knowledge and experience in Customs regulations.

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

MAPLE ETANOL S.R.L.- (www.maple.com.pe)

2010 - 2013

## Administration & Logistics Manager

Responsible for organizing and managing all Administration and Logistics, including IT, Procurement Imports & Transport required for Maple's Ethanol Project in the north of Peru. The project based on producing ethanol from sugar cane.

- Full responsibility for the procurement, import and transport of all equipment & materials needed by project management to build the 100,000 gallon/day ethanol production Plant.
- Responsible for ensuring appropriate and accurate controls for fertilizer, transport, storage and distribution to the fields (8,700 ha sugar cane plantation).
- Responsible for procurement of all agriculture equipment, from international and local distributors as well as all spare parts for proper maintenance for 24 hour operation in fields.
- Responsibility administrating transport for over 450 field workers on the 11,000 hectares dedicated to planting, irrigation and harvesting sugar cane.
- Responsible for implementing company procedures on procurement of materials and services, warehousing, vehicle usage and IT.

Eduardo Phudrer Sousa 2

# MAPLE GAS CORPORATION del PERU S.R.L.- (www.maple.com.pe)

2008 - 2010

# Corporative Material & Logistics Manager

Responsible for Logistics, Procurement & Transport Areas in charge of all, material management, transportation, logistics, inventory control and warehousing for the Maple Energy Group Companies; Maple Gas and Maple Ethanol

O&M for Aguaytia Energy del Perú S.R.L. – Operates Gas field, Gas Plant, Fractionation Plant and Pipe Lines

- Full responsibility for logistics, mobilization and demobilization of Rig to site (truck, river and helicopter). Procurement of all drilling consumables spares and auxiliary equipment for the new Maple Rig for the deep exploration well Santa Rosa 1X.
- Responsible for ensuring appropriate and accurate shipping and storage of all production, construction and maintenance materials, including transit / imports implementing procurement, material management, inventory control and warehousing company procedures.
- Direct participation in organizing and implementing procurement transport & inventory control for the Maples Ethanol Project in the north of Peru.
- Manage substantial savings in personnel and cargo transport to sites.

# AGUAYTIA ENERGY GROUP - Peru (www.aguaytia.com)

# Material & Logistics Manager

1996 - 2008

Responsible for the Logistics Department in charge all procurement, material management, logistics,, inventory control and warehousing for the Aguaytia Energy Group sister companies.

Aguaytia Energy del Perú S.R.L. - Operates Gas field, Gas Plant, Fractionation Plant and Pipe Lines

**Termoselva S.R.L.** – Operates a gas fired 170MW Generation Plant.

Eteselva S.R.L. – Operates 398 Km Transmission Lines.

Gas Integral S.R L. – Operates Gas Transport Feet.

- Responsible for procurement and logistics during the \$286 mm Aguaytia Gas Project construction, and contractor's supervision during shipping and delivering gas plant, power plant and transmission lines components to sites.
- Full responsibility for implementing procurement, material management, inventory control and warehousing company procedures.
- Direct participation in organizing and implementing company's Maintenance, Procurement & Inventory Control software (Oracle Financial) and all Standard Operation Procedures.
- Manage substantial savings in air and ocean freight by consolidating cargo for different areas and expand scope for potential international suppliers.

# THE MAPLE GAS CORPORATION del PERU – Peru (www.maple.com.pe) *Material & Logistics Manager*

1994 - 1996

# Organize and Managed the Logistics Area after taking over the operation for the Peruvian Government by The Maple Corp.

- Supervised all Inventory control take over from Government and oversee the Operation initial requirements.
- Facilitated strategic planning and positioning on the Market for Maple Companies.
- Special support implementing the procedures for the first integrated \$285 mm oncoming Aguaytia Gas Project including the 170 MW power plant and the 398 km transmission lines.

Eduardo Phudker Sousa 3

# PETROPERU SA -Peru

## Camp Supervisor

1983 - 1994

4 years Oil Field Camp Supervisor in the Peruvian jungle, responsible of all services provided at the camp to the Operations Personnel (180), supervise maintenance for camps (6), water plants and services provided by Catering Companies -4 years Transport Supervisor Talara Operations, mob and de-mob work-over rigs and personnel transport -3 years Logistics Supervisor Lima office.

- Organize schedules for maintenance services at Camps and water plants.
- Supervise Catering companies and transport of food supplies to in all Camps in the operation.
- Supervise maintenance personnel and distribute assignments.
- Responsible of providing on time supplies and maintenance personnel for the smaller camps and pump stations (6).

# HAMILTON OIL COMPANY -Peru

1982 - 1983

### Logistics Supervisor

Oil Field Logistics Supervisor in the Peruvian jungle, responsible of all air and river transportation of supplies to drilling sites.

- Organize and optimize tug boat and barges scheduled services for heavy supplies and fuel transport to sites.
- Install and maintain jet fuel supply unit for helicopters.
- Supervise tug boat their party contracts during drilling operations.

## OWNER SERVICES LIMITED - Spain-England

# Area Manager

1974 - 1982

# Management and Maintenance of developed 230-apartment condominium, responsible for all services provided to company clientele.

 Responsible for Owners accounting and all clientele travel arrangements through company's charter planes.

Supported marketing strategies in all company's major resorts through local advertising and coordinated promotional activities with property sales department.

### **EDUCATION**

Santa Maria High School 1960 - 1965 Peruvian University Ricardo Palma – Lima - Peru Mechanical Engineer 1971

# OTHER STUDIES AND TRAINING COURSES

Administration Principles - OSL training center London	1980
Personnel Supervision – Petro-Peru training center Peru	1983
Administration and Productivity – Petro-Peru training center Peru	1986
Problem Analysis and Decision Taking – Petro-Peru training center Peru	1990
Strategic E-Sourcing - Berkley center Peru	2001
Critical Thinking and Decision Making – Berkeley center Peru	2002

### **LANGUAGES**

Fluent in English and Spanish.